Look in the mirror
Checking my face
사람은 쉽게 안 변해
Don't need a hero
Get outta my way
마음 가는 대로
Born to be brave
But it took a long, long time
To realise that I
별빛처럼 찬란한
꽃이 피게 할 거야
Just a little bit different
정답이 뭔데?
No, no, 정해진 건 없는데
Typical, logical
전부 똑같애
I'm gonna do what I wanna do
Dance all night
Until I feel alive
I think I'm ready
I think I'm ready to
Be myself
Not like everybody else
That's not my style
I'd rather, rather, rather be wild
I keep it wild, I keep it free
I got that dangerous in me
Hit the rodeo, that superstar, that one and only
Glowing, shining like a diamond
Trust me, you can't beat this
Baby, I'mma monster
Leave 'em in the dust, then I blow them a kiss (Mwah, mwah)
But it took a long long time
To realise that I
별빛처럼 찬란한
꽃이 피게 할 거야
Just a little bit different
정답이 뭔데?
No, no, 정해진 건 없는데
Typical, logical
전부 똑같애
I'm gonna do what I wanna do
Dance all night
Until I feel alive
I think I'm ready
I think I'm ready to
Be myself
Not like everybody else
That's not my style
I'd rather, rather, rather be wild
I keep it wild, I keep it free
I got that dangerous in me
Hit the rodeo, that superstar, that one and only
Glowing, shining like a diamond
Trust me, you can't beat this
Baby, I'mma monster
Leave 'em in the dust, then I blow them a kiss (Mwah, mwah)
Wild, wild, wild
I'd rather be wild
Be myself, not like everybody else
I'd rather, rather, rather be wild